[theme music playing]
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
NORTH HAMGYONG PROVINCE. NORTH KOREA
Oh. wow!
EPISODE 4
GEUMGANG ORPHANAGE
Hello. children.
My name is Major Ri Eung Ryeong.
and I'm with our nation's great military.
Nice to meet you.
We've brought you all here
because we've been looking
for the nimblest
and most athletic students in the country.
So if you think you have what it takes
to join the team.
and be a part of
the greatest athletic group
that's ever been formed.
then step forward now.
If I join the team. sir.
will I be able to eat my fill?
[chuckles]
Till you die.
YOUNG REVOLUTIONARIES
OF THE LEARNING-FIRST DOCTRINE
We should move the desks too.
-[grunts. groans]
-[panting]
You'll be the only one to pass.
State your name.
[panting]
I'm Park Yeong Gwang. mister.
Let's get the kid ready to leave.
[soldier] Yes. sir.
All right. you heard him.
[panting]
We should take this boy too.
He's got a lot of fight in him.
We can always use a warrior
with his resolve.
Hey.
What's your name. warrior?
Kim…
-[gunshot]
-[birds squawking]
ARMED WITH REVOLUTIONARY SPIRIT
[commander] Stand straight! Attention!
[Eung-reyong] Congratulations.
From this day forward.
you belong to the new special forces unit
of the greatest country in the world.
Now listen up. men.
Your mission is to infiltrate the South.
kill any rats.
and bring the heads
of their leaders to me.
Take them to the torture room.
[recruits] I am not my name.
I am not my body.
I am not my will.
I am nothing but part of the whole.
[commander] Quiet!
I think you two might still be confused
about where you are.
This is hell.
You can survive and join us.
or die and become pig feed!
It's one or the other.
Number 66.
Tell me. what's your name?
I don't remember.
Seventy-three.
How about you? What is your name?
Kim…
I just remember that Kim is my…
[commander] Looks like this punk
is still not broken in.
Do wild animals have names?
Do they?
Listen. You boys have no use
for things like names anymore.
Got it?
Answer me!
-[grunting]
-[blows landing]
[recruits] One. two three. four!
One. two three. four!
-One. two three. four!
-[commander] Come on. move it!
Hurry! Run!
[clamoring]
-[commander] Fire!
-[gunshot]
[exclaiming]
[Kim exclaims]
[wind whistling]
CRUSH THE PROVOCATIVE SCHEMES
OF THE SOUTH KOREAN PUPPETS!
[exclaims]
[Eung-reyong] Stop.
Sixty-six.
You have shown over and over
that you are our countries best.
Well done.
I don't need it.
Go away.
I'm not trying to insult you.
-[sighs]
-You're always losing to me
so I thought it was because
you weren't being fed enough.
Get lost.
Thing is. we're from the same orphanage.
aren't we?
Why are you being so prideful. comrade?
Shut the fuck up!
Bastard! Go shove it down your throat!
[recruit] Those brats are fighting again.
Get over here!
-[exclaims. grunts]
-[clamoring]
COMBAT READINESS IS A REVOLUTIONARY DUTY
[exclaiming]
Get over here. [grunting]
…NUMBER 85. NUMBER 18. NUMBER 44
[exclaiming]
[grunting]
[screams]
[screaming]
[Eung-reyong] With these
two finest warriors ever assembled.
victory will be inevitable.
Complete the mission. men.
and when you return to the Motherland.
you will be welcomed as heroes!
[recruits] Long live
the Democratic People's Republic of Korea!
GANGWON PROVINCE. REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Wait here.
[Eung-reyong] Your brother was
the best agent this unit has ever seen.
He did things
that will never be accomplished again.
But during a high-stakes mission.
a traitorous rat stabbed him in the back
and 66 died in action.
[groans]
[groaning]
[Eung-reyong]
That rat tricked his closest comrade
and he left him to die there alone.
That cockroach became number 66
only to turn into a traitorous mutt
of the South!
[young Gang Seong] Yeong! Yeong!
[crying]
Yeong. why are you leaving me here?
Don't worry!
I swear I'll come back for you.
So you better be here!
You have to survive. okay?
-Yeong!
-Stay alive. Gang Seong!
[cries]
Yeong!
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
[gun clicks]
[sighs]
I finally found you.
Fake 66.
[grunts]
[whispers] Is that? Shit.
Don't move!
Hands up.
Hands up now!
Put the gun down.
Everything's so convenient now. [chuckles]
-Wait. slow down.
-[Sang-a] What's wrong?
There it is. We got our clue.
Drive back slowly. Slow.
Put the gun down.
Listen closely.
Hands on your and get on your knees.
Did you see how cool they busted in?
The mark of a true professional.
Well. she's a co-worker.
And that guy…
-owns a local dry cleaners.
-What?
You don't look too surprised.
Have you known for a while?
Well. I figured I was being watched.
I just didn't know it was you.
You need to surrender. 66.
Let's be smart.
Mr. Kim.
you violated the terms you agreed to.
Surrender now.
Min-ji has…
been kidnapped. sir.
Please just let me find her first.
After that. I'll come in without a fight.
But right now.
my daughter needs me.
Wait. but…
No. hold on.
[stammers] Mr. Kim!
Mr. Kim!
[grunting]
[wincing]
[melancholic music playing]
[gasping]
You okay? Are you hurt?
-Bulletproof vest.
-Seriously?
-I really thought you died.
-Hey. can you help me stand?
-You're fine. Come on.
-[wheezing] I've just been shot. you know.
[Song-a] Stop being dramatic.
I could have died.
[groans]
[Kim grunting]
You're luck you're okay.
Also. when did you even get shot?
Do you have a first aid kit?
It's under the. uh… Wait. no.
You need a hospital.
No. it's just a scratch. so no.
No hospital.
Hey. did you forget there's a bullet
inside of you?
Huh? A bullet wound
is not just a scratch. man.
Seriously? What's a Band-Aid gonna do?
[Jin-cheol] Here. here. here! Right here!
This is good. Let me out here.
[grunts] Thank you. sir.
Hey!
[Han-soo] Did the bleeding stop?
Stop!
-[tires screeching]
-Whoa! Whoa!
Han-soo! [grunts]
What happened?
[winces]
You seriously just almost ran me over!
-What are you. a deer?
-You need to watch where you're going.
-Why would you jump out…
-Even if it only nicked…
Will you let me talk first? Hey!
What the hell's going on. guys?
What happened to Min-ji? Where is she?
Who did this? Huh?
I swear to God…
Whoever those bastards are… [grunts]
Oh. they're so screwed.
When I find…
-Hey. can I break this thing?
-Do it gently.
[groans] I just… [grunts]
-All right. Let's focus.
-[breathing heavily]
[Jin-cheol] You okay back there?
Are you…
Hey!
Is that a gunshot wound?
Wait. they got you already?
How many times have I said to be careful?
Man. what would you guys
do without me. huh?
[groans]
Don't worry. your big brother's here.
You'll be okay.
Think of it
as just another hole in your body.
It's totally normal.
A bullet hole. a butt hole and nostrils
are all holes.
so you're saying it's all the same thing
to you. is that right?
[laughs] Okay.
I'm just saying. you know?
Well. it's not like
we've never been shot before.
Whatever. Just drive!
[Han-soo] You okay. Kim?
-[Jin-cheol] So where we going again?
-[Han-soo] Hwasin Station.
That's where we'll find the homeless guy
who found Min-ji's phone.
SEONMIN-EUP
[Jang] We have 66's current location.
8-3. Gongdan-gil. Seonmin-eup.
Park Jin-cheol is with them now.
-Step on it. Hurry.
-Yes. sir.
Hey. brat.
Get me some more soju.
What? What are you looking at?
Want me to teach you a lesson? [spits]
-Hey. Dad!
-[father] Coming!
-What's going on?
-I'll beat you up. kid.
[teen] I was just walking by
and this man yelled at me.
Yelled at you? For what?
To get him soju.
Hey. sir. You awake?
Sir.
Can I help you?
Do you remember this cell phone?
You traded it for a bottle of soju.
I did?
Okay. So what?
-Where'd you find it?
-Bet he stole it.
[vagrant] "Stole it"? Come on.
Don't hurt my feelings.
What do you take me for. huh?
I found it.
You did? Do you remember where?
Well. why do I have to tell you guys
anything at all?
Don't you know it's a crime
to sell someone else's phone?
-Should I report this guy?
-[chuckles]
Yeah. report it.
Tell the police how three grown men
are harassing one innocent homeless guy.
I should call too.
Let's just punch this guy till he talks.
-Easy.
-That's not a bad idea.
but people are already looking at us.
Well. there's an alley over there.
You guys wait here.
I'll make this quick. okay?
-All right. let's go.
-[stammers]
-Move fast.
-Okay. someone threw it away.
I saw a man put it in the trash.
so I took it.
Please tell me you saw their face.
This looks expensive.
Hey. sir.
Ta-da.
Wanna make a trade?
I'm not a criminal. okay?
After I scored the soju.
I don't know what happened.
Think hard. sir.
The car color.
Or the license plate number.
Do you remember anything?
What about what they looked like?
How many were there?
How the hell could anyone know?
Sir. I'm begging you. Try to remember.
Please give me something.
Well. the car was a white BMV.
I'm not sure the plate number though.
When was this?
The middle of the night.
I don't know what time.
Uh…
He had a ponytail.
I-I promise that's all I know.
[reporter] In Myeongpo Port today.
the forecast calls for mostly clear skies
during the day
with a storm coming in at night.
The localized downpour
is expected to be accompanied
by thunder and lightning late tonight.
so caution is advised.
Hello. boss.
Hey. rookie.
Actually found a good warehouse for once.
-Thank you. sir.
-So this is it?
Did you eat dinner?
Yeah. I just ate. sir.
Gang-min. have we had dinner yet?
No. sir. We haven't had anything all day.
Right. but the rookie went ahead
and had dinner already.
It's disrespectful to eat
before your elders. you know.
I'm sorry. boss.
[laughs] I'm just kidding.
So what'd you eat?
Well. I had sundae gukbap. sir.
Spicy or what?
No. but it was still really good.
Well. you should cool down anyway!
-[laughing]
-[water splashing]
[rookie coughing]
Get your ass out of there
once you've cooled down.
-We don't have time to mess around.
-[rookie] I can't swim!
-Should we move the body now?
-[Gang-min laughs]
Let's eat first. It's not going anywhere.
[chuckles]
Sounds good to me.
We don't know have a lot of info.
so let's just start with the car.
Okay.
White BMV…
-Wait. is that him?
-[Jin-cheol] You found the driver?
-Can you see his face?
-Let me zoom.
Loading now.
Kim Sang-man. 41 years old.
He has eight prior convictions.
[Jin-cheol] Really? Eight priors for what?
I bet they're all assault.
He sounds like an animal.
Wait a minute.
He got out of the back seat
so he wasn't alone.
Good catch.
So with all of the vehicle's details.
I can plug them in here
and find its location.
Hold on.
SEARCHING…
Searching. It's in real time
so it can take a while.
-[sighs]
-[Jin-cheol] How dare they kidnap Min-ji?
I'll make 'em pay. Kim Sang-man.
[groaning]
The hell?
You're trying to kill me?
Body's been secured
and the location's been set.
Now we just need to tie this
to Ju Gang-chan
and we'll be good to go.
[sighs] "Hey. Gang-chan.
They say your daughter…
killed someone on accident."
[laughing]
Hey. sir. I still don't understand
why you're so obsessed with him. boss.
Well. the question is.
how badly was he screwed over?
[laughs] Here boss.
The biggest potato goes to you.
[breathes shakily]
Whoa. whoa. whoa!
I'm sorry. sir! I'm sorry!
[grunting]
Please. sir. I'm sorry!
9 YEARS AGO
-[clamoring]
-[protestor] Go away! Get out of here!
Come on. I'll take on all of you! [grunts]
STOP RECONSTRUCTION
THAT DESTROYS CITIZENS' LIVES
Do you know how old
these apartment buildings are?
I'm not sure. boss.
They were built 40 years ago.
And yet they still
won't approve the redevelopment.
We need that approval so you and I
can get the money
that we're owed for our services.
[chuckles]
You're right. sir.
I wonder how many of these
still don't have a parking garage.
[exclaims]
-[crashes]
-[car alarm blaring]
[reporter] Behind me is the site
where a cleaner fell
from a balcony at Midu Apartments.
After being transported to the hospital.
the victim was taken into surgery
and remains unresponsive.
still in critical care.
The owner of the building
has declined to comment.
Residents have been voicing their concerns
as they complain
that the dangerously low railing
makes the walkway unsafe.
Also. cracks across the exterior walls
have been found.
so residents claim that repair work alone
can no longer hold the building together.
After failing to pass review for years.
the redevelopment of Midu Apartments
has finally been green lit.
The announcement of the approval
was given by the government
on the 19th.
who also issued a maintenance plan
to continue to keep it safe.
Experts say this approval
for the redevelopment of the apartments…
[groaning]
Look. man.
I was just doing what I was told.
Jung-dae. you have to believe me.
-I swear I… [groans]
-[grunts]
[groans]
[Jung-dae]
This isn't how I wanted to go freelance.
CEO YANG SEOK-CHEOL
Ah. shit.
Who knew that it would be so easy
to take the throne?
I should've done this sooner.
[people cheering]
Trust in me alone.
Don't cross me.
Here's to our success.
To us.
[cheering]
-[Jung-dae] Tell the girls to come.
-[underling] Yes. sir.
[cheering]
-Boss. you got a call.
-[phone buzzing]
Hey. [shushes]
Who's this?
[Nam] This is Juhak Construction.
The chairman would like to meet with you.
Heard there's been a change in management.
You used to work for Mr. Yang. right?
[sighs] Listen. young man.
I know who you are.
I know what you can do.
You're gonna be useful to me.
[sighs]
You know. I forgot you even existed.
It was you. right? [blows]
You were the coward
who gave the order to Yang. weren't you?
Stand down.
I believe there's a misunderstanding.
I never gave him that order.
All I said was that I wish someone
would just jump off and die there.
-That's all.
-What?
[chuckles] Geez.
Yang was seriously incompetent. wasn't he?
He couldn't even kill you.
Show no mercy.
[exclaiming]
Die. motherfucker!
[grunts]
[choking]
[shouting. grunting]
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts. groans]
[grunts]
When I was a kid.
my next-door neighbor had a huge dog.
Unfortunately it was feral
and bit the owner one too many times.
Eventually. the owner snapped
and tried to beat the poor dog to death.
But I managed to persuade them
to give it to me.
I actually liked the dog.
because it was feral.
[fire crackling. sizzling]
Do you know how
I was able to tame that dog?
I made sure it could never
bite its owner again.
[ominous music playing]
[groans]
-[tool clicking]
-[Jung-dae groaning]
[Jung-dae gasps]
[whimpers]
Say. "Ah."
[grunting. groaning]
[shouting]
So do you feel like being a good boy now?
I could pour boiling water
down your throat.
then you really
won't be able to bark again.
[groaning]
I'll do anything.
[breathes shakily]
Please. I'll be your dog.
I'll do whatever you say. sir.
Whatever you want.
[crying] Just please let me live.
[crying]
It'll be dark soon.
Let's tidy up
and get ready to move the body.
-Okay. [groans]
-Yes. sir.
-[Gang-min groans]
-[cutlery clatters]
[tense music playing]
Oh. geez. can you stop being so butthurt
about a couple of punches?
Want me to call your mom?
No. I'm perfectly fine. sir!
Boss. we're here now!
-[Jung-dae] Yeah. I have eyes. you idiot!
-[Gang-min] Of course. sir!
[grunts]
Damn. I forgot how heavy dead bodies are.
Stop whining.
[guard] Hey. freeze!
What are you doing here?
What is that?
[inhales deeply]
-It's a dead girl.
-What?
A dead girl?
[sighs]
At your age. you should already be
in bed by now. Jesus.
Sang-man. go.
Yes. sir.
[both groan]
It's not what you think. sir.
We rented this freezer warehouse to. uh…
I'll just show you the contract.
Where is it?
[ominous music plays]
[guard] What are you doing?
It's still not done yet?
How much longer now?
I promise it's almost done.
We just hit…
eighty one percent.
[Jin-cheol sighs] This is taking forever.
-[blade slicing]
-[guard grunting. groaning]
-[pants]
-[guard groans]
Damn. Hurry up.
[both grunting]
[Han-soo] Ninety-five.
Ninety-six.
[sighs]
What the hell?
Isn't that the Silent Cricket?
Who?
[beeping rapidly]
[metal creaking]
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
[grunts]
[Sang-man sighs] Man…
[laptop chimes]
[tense music playing]
MYEONGPO PORT. REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Hurry up and get out!
I know you're alive. Agent Kim.
Stalling is just going to
make everything worse.
Coming with me is better than
being dragged back to the North
and getting killed. right?
Come on out!
[car door creaks]
[groaning]
[panting]
I asked for Agent Kim. didn't I?
-[car door closes]
-Come out now!
Gotta say.
as soon as I saw you
with that stupid fedora.
I knew you were trouble.
[sucks teeth] You have no idea
what kind of hole you're digging.
doing something like this.
I have no choice.
I'll make sure that you truly understand
the real meaning of pain and suffering.
you dick.
Just give me a sec.
-[tense music plays]
-[knee cracks]
[scoffs]
-Really?
-[groans] I have to.
-I'm not young anymore. [groans]
-[back cracks]
And my back's been killing me lately.
[groans]
But even though I need to stretch now.
I can still kick your ass.
Stop wasting my time and move.
Hey. asshole. don't you know who I am?
Yeah.
Silent… Oh.
Silent Rat. right? [chuckles]
[singsongy] Silent Rat is here.
I knew that was you!
With his fedora.
-he found it in some poo.
-[gun cocks]
[chuckles. grunts]
[dramatic music plays]
I still got it.
Rock 'n Roll.
-Did you see that?
-Yeah. you missed.
Those fancy moves
don't work in a real fight.
Thought they did.
Oh. well.
At least I managed to distract you.
Idiot Cricket.
[engine starts]
[Guk-cheol] Agent Kim!
[upbeat. dramatic music plays]
[grunting]
[music stops]
Oh. come on.
Did you really have to pull that out?
You're that scared of me?
Let's go.
[music resumes]
[groans]
[sighs] This sucks.
Well. you know.
the hero always shows up at the end
to save the day.
Han-soo you got this.
Show him the power of Taekwondo.
[panting]
I'm happy you're not a waste of
taxpayer money.
Let's see how you fight with only one leg.
-Oh… Is that?
-What the…
Hey! The director is fighting
Sung Han-Soo on the bridge. Hurry up!
Wow. you brought a gun. a knife.
and even an entourage?
I'm sick of hearing your voice.
[grunting]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
You ever been bungee jumping?
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[grunts]
Hey. Jin-cheol. I'm off!
[exclaims]
-Director!
-Sir!
-Look. there he is!
-What do we do?
[tailor] He can't swim. can he?
I guess it's my turn to go now.
Two. four. six. eight. ten…
Fourteen of them.
How easy.
I give up.
Peace!
I want peace!
[tires squeal]
Min-ji.
Stay alive. okay?
Dad's coming.
[yelping]
[coughs]
[Min-ji] Hello?
Is there… [coughs]
Is there anyone there?
[breathes shakily]
There's someone in here!
I'm… I'm trapped in here!
[exhales sharply]
JU GANG-CHAN'S LACKEY
[Jung-dae] I've got you by the balls now.
Asshole Nam isn't answering
any of my calls.
-Hey. Sang-man.
-Yes. boss?
Head over to the warehouse
and go take a picture for me.
And not just a picture of the body.
we need a selfie.
Hey.
You know what a money shot is. right?
Uh-huh.
So just in case.
take a picture of the girl.
and then one of myself. right?
You moron.
[dog barks in distance]
You have to take a selfie like this so…
-Oh.
-[sighs] Forget it.
[groans] I'll just do it.
Stupid.
Go do something
instead of just playing with your hair.
God. you're useless.
-[Gang-min] Hey.
-What?
It's the selfie first.
then the body. you idiot.
Screw you.
[line ringing]
They can't do anything right.
[clicks tongue]
[phone buzzing]
[sighs]
Hey. Nam. finally.
Why didn't you pick up my call?
What. don't you miss me?
Well. I miss you.
and I was just thinking about
sending you something.
but I don't know if I should.
Just get to the point.
I just wanted to catch up
with an old friend.
So. what's up. you weasel-faced bastard.
are you holding up well or what?
Don't annoy me.
-[laughing]
-[intriguing music playing]
Okay. okay. Geez. you can be so scary.
Look. the Chairman and I have business
that we need to discuss. okay?
So put Chairman…
I mean.
put that Gang-chan bastard on the phone.
You really do have a death wish.
Where are you?
The one with the death wish
is that asshole's daughter.
She killed someone not too long ago.
If he doesn't want his precious
little angel eating prison food.
then tell him to reach out
as soon as he can.
[chuckles] Don't worry. I'll take
good care of the body till he wants it.
[laughing]
Wait… the body?
[call disconnects]
[phone buzzes]
WORTHLESS THUG
VOICE RECORDING
[Jung-dae] So you're saying
that you killed this girl?
[Hye-ri] Get rid of her.
Can you handle that or not?
[Jung-dae] Whoa… [scoffs]
…I was just asking a question.
why are you talking to me like that?
[Hye-ri] Don't worry about the money.
-I'll give you whatever you want.
-No way!
I'm gonna pretend
like I never heard this. okay?
Now leave!
[Hye-ri crying]
I-I was just studying in a private room.
And when I stepped out for a break.
she showed up out of nowhere.
yelling at me.
[breathing shakily]
So you killed her?
No-No. Dad! It was her own…
I only lightly pushed her out of my way.
but she tripped and then she…
[breathes shakily]
I think she did it on purpose.
She's putting on an act
so she can get money from me.
Dad!
You saw how much of a psycho she was.
She bullied me every day.
I'm the victim here.
None of this is my fault. Dad!
[inhales deeply]
I expect you to always be honest with me.
So tell the truth.
That girl…
did you kill her?
I think I did. sir.
[cries]
[yelps]
[sobs]
If you wanted to kill her so badly.
you should have asked me to do it.
Did you think I wouldn't do that for you?
I've always given you
everything you've asked for.
I'm so disappointed in you.
[crying] I apologize.
You're forgiven.
It's okay.
And you're sure that she's dead?
[breathes shakily]
I mean. she was bleeding from her head.
I'm not sure.
[ominous music plays]
So Golden Teeth said
he has the body. right?
Yes.
Then let's make it easy
and say he killed her.
Understood. sir.
[sniffles]
[Min-ji grunting]
Hello?
Please open the door!
Is anyone there?
Please let me out!
[inhales sharply. cries]
[grunts]
[shakily] Someone let me out…
[crying softly]
-[tires screech]
-[gear shifts]
[tense music plays]
[pulls hand brake]
So cold…
Oh. Dad…
[breathes shakily]
[groans] So cold…
[door creaking]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[Sang-man] Can I help you?
-Who the hell is this guy?
Hey. who are you? Are you lost?
-You're in the wrong place.
-Can't you hear us? [scoffs]
NAME: KIM SANG-MAN
AGE: 41
Does this asshole need his hearing aid
or something? Geez.
Who the hell are you. huh? [scoffs]
[chuckling]
Maybe he's just stupid. who knows.
You remember this girl. right?
Where is she?
[sighs heavily]
[blows nose]
This bastard's got me
working overtime now.
-You chose this. okay? Huh? [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
[groaning]
First I take a left…
[exhales heavily]
It's damn cold.
Even a corpse
would freeze to death in here.
[exhales]
Where the hell did they put it? Huh?
[suspenseful music plays]
[phone buzzing]
JU GANG-CHAN
[whimsical music plays]
[groans]
[buzzing continues]
[breathing shakily]
[door closes]
-[buzzing continues]
-[sighs]
Oh. wow. Hey. Chairman.
I can't believe you called me directly.
You doing good?
I mean. I know you're stuffing your face
with the best food the world can offer.
so I'm sure you're doing better than I am.
Nam told me everything already.
My daughter really owes you one.
Oh. please.
She doesn't owe me anything. sir.
It was nothing.
I kind of miss that little princess.
Is she doing well?
You know.
She really is just like you. sir.
I bet you're proud of your daughter
becoming such a great killer.
Oh. and she even knows
who to call afterwards.
You know you've really earned
the title of Father of The Year.
Let's meet. asshole.
That's what I was gonna say.
But Gang-chan. you better start treating
me with a little respect. asshole.
Can't you see what's going on?
I'm about to send you an address.
After this call. go there
with two billion won in cold hard cash.
And don't bring any of your goons.
Come alone or it's off.
Oh. and one more thing.
Go pull out all of Nam's teeth
and give them to me as a gift. okay?
[inhales sharply]
Can you send a picture of you doing it?
Tell him I'll give him private lessons
on how to talk without his teeth
cause I've learned a few tricks
along the way.
[chuckles]
[call disconnects]
-Let's get going.
-Yes. sir.
[dramatic music playing]
Roll out!
-Yes. sir!
SHARING LOCATION WITH KIM MIN-JI
[Jung-dae] 23. Hangman 10-ro.
[sucks teeth]
I really wish I could've been there
in person to see that asshole cry.
Should I tell Gang-chan to do it here?
[door creaking]
[grunting. groans]
[groans]
[yells]
[dramatic music playing]
["GO! GO!" playing]
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
[Jung-dae] I'm sorry. Don't hurt me!
[Min-ji] Dad. I'll stay alive.
[Kim] I'm in a hurry. so bring it.
Don't you think we need weapons
for this mission?
In the end. his ultimate weakness
is his daughter.
Split up and find her.
[Ju] The dog's been taken of.
all I have to do now
is erase you from this world.
[Kim] If it's true that my Min-ji is dead.
none of you…
will make it out of here.
[Min-ji] I'm sorry. Dad.
-[Kim] Min-ji is…
-[thunderclap]
…alive.